the destruction of
уничтожением
Bato was carried out by both sides I will
Бато занимались обоюдно две стороны я
say so No once again Ukraine find don't
так скажу Нет ещё раз Украина находи не
wait
подожди
Ukraine is an achievement of two ro once again
Украина это достижение двух ро ещё раз
what two sides look Ukraine was
каких двух сторон смотрите Украина была
in Bakhmut always Yes Ukraine did not
в бахмуте всегда Да Украина не
capture Bakhmut don't come it was
захватывала бахмут не приходи она была
there Russia wiped it off the face of the
там Россия стёрла его с лица
earth for whom do I understand correctly Don't
земли ради кого я правильно понимаю Не
look I understand correctly that Russia
смотри я правильно понимаю что Россия
liberate Bakhmut yes
освобождай бахмута да
Hello Good evening I am from the city of
Здравствуйте Добрый вечер я из города
Khmelnitsky where are you
Хмельницке Вы
from I think we have already communicated but
откуда по-моему с вами уже общались а
I am not there I think Nila you are talking
нету меня там по-моему Нила вы говорите
about Vakha Well now it's
у Ваха Ну сейчас
fine I am from Germany and
нормально я из Германии а в Германию
where did you
откуда
get to Germany in Siberia Well where is Siberia from is a
попали в Сибири Ну откуда Сибирь - это
very stretching concept
очень растяжитель понятие
Well yes Siberia is big everything is
Ну да Сибирь большая всё
correct with Omsk region have you heard such
правильно с Омская область слышали такое
Omsk Well Omsk Omsk Tom heard yes yes
Омская Ну Омск Омск Том слышал да да
yes I understood listen from Khmelnitsky
да понял слушайте от Хмельницка
Shepetovka Shepetovka how far is 100
Шепетовка Шепетовка сколько далеко 100
km Oh listen next to us here we are in Slavuta
км О слушайте рядышком вот мы в Славуте
in Shepetovka every summer we vacationed there
в Шепетовке каждое лето отдыхали там
my aunt lives And where exactly in  Slavuta
меня тётя жит А где именно в Славуте
were on holiday and there in the centre through the centre of
отдыхали а там в центре через центр
Slavuta there is a river like this
славуты проходит река такая
rye and it has a house Direct here Direct on the
ры вот а у неё дом Директ вот Директ на
river Yes and on the other side there is a
речке Да а вот с другой стороны
restaurant I think plyaucha Iva or Iva
ресторан по-моему плакуча Ива или Ива
or Iva then it was called at that time I understood
или ива тогда то время называлось понял
And whose km what do you
А чей км как
think Well don't you know whose
считаете Ну а вы разве не знаете чей
Crimea is I know that it is Ukrainian but
Крым Я знаю что украинский а просто
some Russians just think differently
некоторые россияне по-другому считают
that's why they
поэтому
ask Well there is Ukrainian money
спрашивают ну там деньги украинские
going around Well for example when Hitler captured
ходят Ну например когда Гитлер захватил
Crimea there was non-Soviet money
Крым там деньги не советские
going around Well let's just
ходили Ну связь
say the connection is just to say whose Crimea is in
скажем просто говорить чей Крым в
Austria people speak German It's
Австрии люди на немецком говорят Это же
not Germany at the moment listen at the
не Германия в данный момент послушайте в
moment there is Russian
момент там Российская
power that is occupied
власть то есть оккупированный
So why do you think that Well it's not me who
Так почему вы считаете что Ну не я
thinks it is your your government the
считаю это ваше ваше правительство
German government thinks that it is
правительство Германии считает что он
occupied Or am I
оккупированный Или я
wrong the German government Yes your
ошибаюсь правительство Германии Да ваша
your country thinks Crimea is Oka this is the first time I've
ваша страна считает Крым Оку первый раз
heard this the first time I've heard this not you look
первый раз такое слушаю не ва смотрите
your country Thank you very much to your
ваша страна Огромное спасибо вашей
country for the support it gives to
стране за поддержку которую она даёт
Ukraine and the thing is that I understand that
Украине и дело в том что я понимаю что
taxation is such a well like a
налогообложение - это такой ну как бы
heavy burden for you  but your taxes
тяжёлое Бремя для вас но с ваших налогов
are used to supply weapons
поставляют
for the destruction of these Russian
у на уничтожение вот этих русских
occupiers,
оккупантов
I would like to express my gratitude to the German people on behalf of all Ukrainians
я сейчас от имени всех украинцев хочу
for the fact that you supply
за то что вы Из года в год поставляется
us with weapons for the Russian occupiers from year to year with
нам вооружение для русских оккупантов с
yours. I understand that of course
ваши Я понимаю что с ваших конечно
not all of Russia can be destroyed with your taxes,
налогов не всю Россию можно да
but some Vanya will be torn from Russia for
но какому-то Ваньке из России оторвут за
your euros. This is very commendable,
конкретно ваши евро это очень похвально
and every person from Germany with whom I
и каждый человек из Германии с которым я
communicate. Yes, even if you do not directly
общаюсь Да вы даже вот если прямо не
support Ukraine. Yes,
поддерживаете Украину Да вы через свои
you finance the denazification of this
налоги вы финансирует денацификация этой
RU through your taxes. Yes, yes, therefore. A huge thank you to your
ру да да поэтому Огромное спасибо вашему
government for sending your taxes
правительству что ваши налоги отправляет
for denazification.
на денацификация
Do you think that people in Ukraine
Как вы считаете в Украине вообще люди
decide anything at all? I do
что-нибудь решают вообще вообще мне
n’t care at all now. I’m not
сейчас всё равно я политикой не
interested in politics. I’ve never been interested. I do
интересуюсь я никогда не интересовался Я
n’t know.
не знаю
Look, I’m not interested in politics at all.
я я смотри я вообще политика не
I’m a financier. I’m interested in
интересуюсь я финансист мне интересно
money from
чтобы деньги из
Germany, your country, coming to
Германии вашей страны приходили на
Russian soldiers. Everything is politics. I don’t go to
русских солдат всё политика я не хожу на
elections. I don’t know who these presidents and
выборы я не знаю кто там эти президенты
deputies are. I’m a simple person. I’m
депутаты я простой человек Меня
interested in my family, my street, and
интересует моя семья да моя улица и
in short, German German aid.
короче немецкая немецкая помощь на
destruction of Russian occupiers you are a
уничтожение русских оккупантов вы
financier of course this is a terrible force
финансист конечно это страшная сила
wait therefore therefore I will say it again
подожди поэтому поэтому я ещё раз скажу
Listen you were talking now Give me
Послушай вы говорили теперь Дайте мне
No I don't interrupt you interrupt me
Нет я не перебивайте вы меня перебивайте
this is very uncultured until the Interlocutor
это очень некультурно пока Собеседник не
has finished You should silently nod listen
договорил Вы должны молча кивать слушать
and speak Ladies and
и говорить Дамы и
gentlemen Therefore I will say
господ Поэтому вот я скажу
Ukraine And you finance Ukraine Yes you
Украину А вы финанси Украину Да вы
share with us the joy
разделяете с нами радость
from I see here we have
от я смотрю вот есть у нас
channels
каналы
posting Russian occupiers and this is
выкладывают русских оккупантов и это
Ukraine Ukrainians are dying from Russian
Украин украинцы погибают от русских
money and from German money they are dying non-Ukrainians are
денег а от немецких погибают не украинцы
dying and yours
погибает и ваши
specifically you specifically you not a single
ко конкретно вы конкретно вы ни одного
Russian soldier I take my hat off to you for this
русского солдата я вам за это снимаю
look you are great because
шляпу смотрите вы молодец потому что за
what I love about democratic countries like
что я люблю демократические страны типа
Germany is that even
Германии что даже
people like you who moved to
таких как вы которые переехали в
Germany but to the Soviet Union and Russia
Германию но на Советский Союз и Россию
yes Even they are forced to finance
да Даже их заставляют финансировать
Yes it's cool look kitty look at
Да это классно смотри котик посмотри
this Yes this
этот Да этот
finances comrade Yes it
финансирует товарищ Да
finances by the way to you today happy
финансирует кстати тебя сегодня с
holiday Happy holiday today May 2nd
праздничком С праздничком сегодня 2 мая
anniversary Day of liberation of Odessa from Roshi
юбилей День освобождения Одессы от роши
where are you  run hello What are you talking about
куда вы бежа здравствуйте Да ты что
again what a surprise Hello
опять какая неожиданность Здравствуй
Andrey hello last time we talked And it
Андрей здра прошлый раз общались Да и
seems like I said that soon drones
вроде я сказал что скоро и до Татарстана
will reach Tatarstan
будут доле
Well they have flown they have
беспилотники Ну долетели
flown What do you think Where are they
долетели Как вы думаете Откуда их
launched from Well I saw photos of these
запускают Ну я видел фотографии этих
drones well they seem
беспилотников ну вроде
to be French or something Yes where would drones be
как французские что ли Да беспилотники
launched from
бы откуда запу
if from Ukraine how did they fly Well I don't
если с Украины как они долетели Ну я не
think from any other Well where from
думаю что с каких-то других Ну откуда с
Kazakhstan You mean Of course not I
Казахстана Вы имеете Конечно нет Я же
also think no if from Ukraine Well of
тоже думаю что нет вот если с Украины Ну
course
конечно
this is a puncture a puncture And this is a puncture I
это ну прокол прокол А это прокол Мне
like this
нравится этот
puncture Well I don't you understand Good well I
прокол Ну мне нет вы же понимаете Хоро
understand Yes we are diametrically different
ну понимаю Да у нас диаметрально разные
Yes we are on Svetlaya you are there well I wouldn't
Да мы на светлой вы там ну я бы не
say And the question is look if this Well
сказал А вопрос смотрите если это Ну
once is a puncture And if it
один раз - это прокол А если раз
flew once into one Oil Refinery
прилетело в один Нефтеперерабатывающий
into the second into the third fourth and it
во второй в третий четвёртый и в
flies to Tatarstan and it flies to Nizhny Novgorod
Татарстан долетает и в Нижний Новгород
then is it a puncture or is it already a
долетает то это прокол или это уже
system Well it means the
системность Ну значит
system is not working  There is something to
система не не дорабатывает Есть над чем
work on, what do you think, the
работать х а как вы думаете с нужно
system needs months to
системе месяцев чтобы
finalize Well, listen Well, the Armed Forces are
доработать Ну слушайте Ну ВС же у
improving You are also not standing
совершенствуется Вы тоже не стоите на
still, you are very creative Judging
месте очень подходите к творчески Судя
by everything, to the question Yes, we are not standing still
по всему к вопросу Да не стоим на месте
At first we were standing still, we thought that now
Сначала мы стояли думали что сейчас
the missiles would stop Russia will come to its senses
ракеты перестанут Россия образумится
Russia does not stop and we are not standing
Россия не перестаёт и мы не стоим на
still, we are flying, we are flying
месте мы летим летим
mm the same is
мм теже
not true Look We noticed that in this no,
не так смотри Мы заметили что в этом нет
it is not us in the opposite direction, it is you in the opposite direction, it was
это не мы обратное направление это вы
flying to us back in
обратное направление к нам летело ещё в
22 and now it has started
двадцать втором году а теперь начало
flying in the opposite direction, it is you in the
летать и в обратном направлении это вы
opposite direction, and so it
обратное направление к нам и так
has been flying Well, since you are on the other side for
прилетало Ну раз вы на той стороне для
you We are in the opposite direction for us, you are in the
вас Мы обратное направление для нас вы
opposite
обратное
direction, [ __ ], it has not started
направление сри сза прилетать не начало
flying to us, it used to fly more
прилетать к нам раньше прилетало больше
now it is flying less already What are you talking about Well,
сейчас меньше прилетает уже Да вы что Ну
yes, I was watching
да я вот смотрел
the news Let's do it So do you also
новости Давайте Так вы помните ещё
remember when there was shelling of the Ukrainian
помните когда были обстрелы украинской
energy sector in 2002 Well, yes, we were
энергетики в ть втором году Ну да онь мы
sitting without electricity, I really had
без света сидели я реально у нас в
electricity cut off in our city too, there were 4 hours, there
городе тоже отключали свет там 4 часа
were 4, there were no, there were no,  Tae
было 4 не было было не было было Тае
four there was no two there was four there was no
четыре не было два было четыре не было
two there were in many cities in general now
два было во многих городах вообще сейчас
somehow in general Everything is simple well something like a
как-то вообще Всё просто ну что-то вроде
bomb but there
бом бите но свет
is light Well okay I'm happy for you but the situation is
есть Ну хорошо я рад за вас но ситуация
that according to the power grid it seems like there are
такая что по энергосистеме вроде бы
strong ones there now nano Well I don't know
сильные там сейчас нано Ну я не знаю
look strong not strong when 2 years
смотрите сильные не сильные когда 2 года
ago or a year and a half ago you hit the
назад или полтора года назад вы ударили
power grid That was strong
по энергосистеме Вот это было сильной
because there really was no light the whole
потому что реально не было света целый
day my city was without light even the
день мой город был без света даже
Internet didn't really catch and then
интернет толком не ловил а потом
they turned it on something for several weeks there was
включили что-то несколько недель было
generally such a very schedule there were 2 hours of
вообще такой очень график там 2 часа
power four did not power and so it
подавали четыре не подавали и так по
was all over Ukraine now well everything
всей Украине было сейчас ну всё
is Well okay Well I'm generally glad
есть Ну хорошо Хорошо я вообще рад тому
that the civilian population that suffer so that they
что мирное население что страда чтобы
suffer as per
страдало как по
Well as little as possible you understand it would be of
Ну как можно меньше понимаете было бы
course
конечно
I wouldn't I wouldn't be happy about that if you
Я бы я бы не радовался Тому если бы вы
were sitting there right the entire city population
сидели там прямо всё городское население
sat all day bomb shelter
сидело целыми днями бомбоубежище Мне бы
It wouldn't give me any joy or
это не доставляло какой-то радости или
pleasure I wouldn't
удовольствия Я бы ну над этим бы не
make fun of it well but does it give you
глумился хорошо а доставляет ли вам
joy or pleasure uh the fact that the
радость или удовольствие ээ то что
population  Bakhmut was liberated from
население бахмута было освобождено от
their
своих
homes well you know this destruction
домов ну вы знаете это уничтожением
was mutually carried out by two sides I will
занимались обоюдно две стороны я так
say so the achievement of two Ron what other two
скажу достижение двух Рон ещ каких двух
sides look Ukraine was always in Bakhmut
сторон смотрите Украина была в бахмуте
Yes Ukraine did not seize Bakhmut
всегда Да Украина не захватывала бахмут
do not come it was there Russia wiped
не приходи она была там Россия стёрла
it off the face of the
его с лица
earth for whom do I understand correctly Don't
земли ради кого я правильно понимаю Не
look I understand correctly that Russia
смотри я правильно понимаю что Россия
liberate Bakhmut
освобождай бахмута
so this is what Donetsk region Yes
так это какая Донецкая область Да
as far as Donetsk region Yes Ukraine
насколько Донецкая область Да Украина
here is Donetsk region now
вот Донецкая область сейчас
Well the
Ну
constitution is constitutional yes yes
консти конституционна циона да да
entered the acts of the Russian Federation still ri
вошла актов российской федераци ещ ри
therefore it goes from our point of view you
поэтому идёт с нашей точки зрения вы
understand correctly once again look look I will
поймите правильно ещё раз смотри смотри
not disconnect you do not interrupt me
не я тебя отключу не перебивай меня
when I interrupt look people lived in
когда я перебиваю смотри люди жили в
Bakhmut they never decided anything to
бахмуте они никогда не решали ничего
join some Russian
присоединяться к какой-то Российской
Federation you wrote that they now
Федерации вы вписали что они теперь
came to the Russian Federation destroyed
Российской Федерации пришли уничтожили
their houses I ask you did you come to
ихние дома Я вас спрашиваю вы пришли их
liberate them as if for their sake or for the sake of
как бы освободить Ради них или Ради
whom and for their sake including for their sake
кого и Ради них в том числе вот Ради них
I understand correctly that to destroy their  the
я правильно понимаю что уничтожить ихний
city is not for
город это не ради
their sake Well, the city was not destroyed on purpose
их Ну целенаправленно город не уничтожал
again I don't know whether it was directed or not
ещё раз я не знаю направлено или не
let's say that people lived in Bakhmut
направ давайте так люди жили в бахмуте
Yes, they lived normally, they walked, they drank, they ate, they
Да жили нормально ходили Гуляли пили ели
got married, they had fun Yes, wait, don't
женились развлекались Да вы подожди не
interrupt me when I interrupt you,
перебивай меня когда я перебиваю тебя
so you came to Bakhmut Why
вот вы пришли в бахмут Для чего
free these people Yes, I don't want to
освободить этих людей Да не хочется в
somehow go into a format of rudeness, so I'll tell
формат как-то грубости переходить вот я
you like that Don't go over to it Look, I
тебя Чуст так Не переходите смотрите я
asked you a question, you came to Bakhmut for the sake of the
ва задал вопрос вы пришли в бахмут ради
people of Bakhmut,
людей
uh, for the liberation of a subject of the
бахмута ээ для освобождения субъекта
Russian Federation Wait, that is, stop, stop,
Российской подожди то есть стоп стоп
you came to protect the people of Bakhmut or to
вы пришли защитить людей бахмута или
take some subject for yourself
забрать себе субъект
According to the request and the
какой-то Согласно просьбе и проведённому
referendum that was held Wait, the people of Bakhmut asked
референдуму подожди люди бахмута просили
you to hold a
вас проводили
referendum Ask the people of Bakhmut No,
референдум спросите у людей бахмута нет
the people of Bakhmut, in short, they are sending
люди бахмута короче посылают
you, unfortunately, look, the people of Bakhmut
вас к сожалению смотри люди бахмута
are sending you because
посылают вас потому что
you, who wiped their city off the face of the
вы которые стёрли с ихний город с лица
earth And you, who are
земли А ты
just sitting and saying a subject
просто который сидит и говоришь субъект
and not a subject, will happen now, yes, will happen now,
а не субъект сейчас будет да сейчас
in short, will happen now Look, yes
будет это короче сейчас будет Смотри да
here is the one that tells the subject and not the
вот который рассказывает субъект и не
subject then you came to protect people or
субъект то вы пришли защитить людей или
take the subject that you
забрать себе субъект который вы
drew including you sound but didn't
нарисовали включая тебе зву а не
have time Hello What are you talking about I
успел Привет О чём общаешься
don't know how it
ту не знаю как
will come cool
придёт прикольно
and what do
а
you have on your mug
ты что у тебя на кружке изображено
more precisely who is this one of our Ukrainian
точнее кто это наш один украинский
singer And what is his name DJ an
певец А как звать его диджей ан
droni I know in rap
дрони Я знаю рэпе у
you have this one in short vre Sai famous in
вас этот короче вре Сай известный в
Ukraine after all
Украине таки
he has a lot of tracks on Spotify in short
таки у него и в Spotify короче куча
I'm just a fan of what
треков Я просто фанат какого
genre What kind of music And he is generally
жанра Что за музыка А он вообще он
unique he is in short in electronic
уникальный он короче и в электронной
music yes DJ and also sings Yes vocals and
музыке да дидже и ещё поёт Да вокал и
A little rock even does
Ещё немного рок даже делает
in short a unique
короче уникальный
type By the way I also listen to electronic music
тип Я кстати тоже электронную музыку
there anything
слушаю там что-нибудь
electronic does not
электрони плохо
charge well And so I like Fomin more
заряжает А так мне больше Фомина
there Fernando Ferreiro and others like
нравится там Фернандо феррейро ещё такие
that I understood what from Ukrainian
вот понял что из украинского
you listen to well what does it have to do with Ukrainian
слушаешь ну причём туто из украинского
Well, I can listen to Monica comes in Yeah
Ну вот Монику могу послушать заходит Угу
MC And so nothing
MC А так ничего
more but zipa just generally depending on the
больше но зипа прямо вообще по
mood It happens depending on the mood sometimes
настроению Бывает под настроени иногда
comes in
заходит
so that's what you are talking about Let
так вот о чём общаетесь Давайте про
's talk about the war or
войну будем говорить или
not Yeah right  let's
нет Да ну давай
talk How do you feel about the fact that
поговорим Как ты относишься к тому что
all Russians don't like us Americans we are
все россияне не любят нас американцев мы
ordinary people what do we have to do with it and you are a Ukrainian
простые люди причём мы ту а вы украинец
I am a US citizen I am a US citizen not
прожи Я гражданин США Я гражданин США не
I was a citizen of the Russian Federation
я был гражданином Российской Федерации
I lived in Rostov 18 years already living in
я жил в Ростове 18 лет уже живу в
America in 2 years will be the twentieth
Америке через 2 года будет двадцатое
citizen of the USA it
гражданином США
turns out And where exactly is California
получается А где именно Калифорния
Sacramento and California is there a desert or
Сакраменто а Калифорния там пустыни или
not no not a desert Well that's where the fires
нет нет не пустыня Ну это там где пожары
were that's where the fires
были это там где пожары
were And I understand I have a lot of damage there yes I will
были А я понял я там ущерба много да
bring a little there is My dacha
принесу немножко есть У меня дача с
burned down I also
горела тоже
understand And what do you
понял А чем
do in America
занимаетесь в Америке преподаватель
university teacher So tell me why you
университета Так расскажи мне почему вы
Russians treat us ordinary
россияне плохо относитесь к нам простым
Americans badly I am loyal Well why
американцам я лояльно отношусь Ну почему
don't you like And we Americans like Why
не любят А мы американцы типа Почему вы
don't you like America
Америку не любите
Americans Well I'm telling you
американцев Ну я же говорю я
I am cold-blooded about America I don't care
хладнокровно отношусь к Америке Мне без
at all and why do you treat Ukrainians badly
вообще а к украинцам почему плохо
Well because there is a special military
Ну потому что специально военная
operation going on and what do you treat
операция идёт и и что относитесь почему
Ukrainians badly it was you who
плохо к украинцам это же вы на них
attacked them and not
напали а не на
you Well formally
вас Ну формально
Yes how  we would have been the first to join so
Да как бы мы мы в первые вступили так то
why do you treat them badly I
почему вы к ним плохо
don't even know what to
относитесь не знаю даже что тебе
answer you Well why do you personally
ответить Ну ты лично почему плохо
treat
относишься к
Ukrainians badly And why did you decide that I
украинцам А почему ты решил что я к ним
treat them badly Well I have such an
плохо отношусь Ну есть у меня такое
assumption
предположение
Yeah right but it's misleading your
Да нуно оно обманчивое твоё
assumption there are bad people there are
предположение есть люди плохие есть
good people Zelensky is bad or good that
хорошие Зеленский плохой или хороший что
Zelensky is bad or
Зеленский плохой или
good Well when he performed on our
хороший Ну когда он выступал у нас на
stage he was probably a good comedian
эстраде наверно хорошим был комиком
now as a politician I have
сейчас как политик я
him Well I have a more negative attitude towards him And
его Ну больше отрицательно к нему отно А
why are you negative Well what
чем почему отрицательно ты Ну что он
did he do bad to you I don't know he made money here
сделал да не знаю тут денег заработал
left nothing bad Why do you have a bad attitude towards
ушёл не что плохого Почему ты плохо к
Zelensky what did he do bad to you I'm
зеленскому что он плохого тебе сделал
just
просто
curious but personally specifically He
интересно но лично конкретно Мне он
didn't do anything bad to me
ничего не сделал плохого
Well I don't
Ну не
know Well you have a bad
знаю Ну вот у тебя в голове плохое
attitude towards
отношение к
Zelensky in your head Well then let's just
зеленскому Ну так давай просто я
figure it out Why where do you Russians get
разбираюсь Почему откуда у вас у Россиян
hatred towards other nations and other
Ненависть к другим народам и к другим
presidents here lived Zelensky Yes he
президентам вот жил се Зеленский Да он
didn't touch you didn't touch Russia but you
не трогал тебя не трогал Россию да вы на
attacked him and he's also bad For you it's a
него напали и ещё он плохой Для вас
joke something you  I'm completely
прикол что-то ты меня вообще в тупик
stumped You attacked Ukraine attacked
загнал Вот вы напали на Украину напали
Zelensky attacked Ukrainians and
на Зеленского напали на украинцев а
bad Ukrainians bad Zelensky bad
плохие украинцы плохой Зеленский плохая
Ukraine what's the joke I have
Украина в чём прикол
no idea Let's think try to think
Без понятия Давай думаем пробуем думать
turn on the gray
включаем серое
matter What Well I like
вещество Какое Ну я как
what Yes gray which is the brain not like
како Да серая которая мозг не то что
brown which is not in the brain And gray
коричневая которая не в мозг А серая
which is in the brain
которая в мозг
I'm just like a teacher at the
включает Я просто как преподаватель в
university if I'm
университете если я
stimulated Yes thinking can't know
стимулируют Да думать не может знать
the answers to all the questions Yes but he must with
ответы на все вопросы Да но он должен с
certain information make up
определённой информацией составлять
facts and make some kind of his own conclusion
факты и делать какое-то своё заключение
not necessarily correct but make
не обязательно правильное но делать
some kind of conclusion That's how you
какое-то умозаключение Вот как ты
think Why you you can
считаешь Почему ты ты же можешь
see Why you are a simple Russian
посмотреть Почему ты простой российский
guy who has never been to Ukraine
парень который никогда не был в Украине
Ukrainians did nothing to him and he
украинцы ему ничего не делали да и он
hates Ukraine hates Zelensky and
ненавидит Украину ненавидит Зеленского и
so
так
on Well because such an aggravation
дальше Ну потому что такое обострение
is happening now what Have you got an aggravation
происходит како У тебя что обострилось у
your temperature rose for example or
тебя температура поднялась например или
there is blood pressure what happened to you that you
там давление что у тебя случилось что ты
don't like
не любишь
Zelensky And are you his fanatic not I'm
Зеленского А вы что его фанатик не мне
just interested I look I live in
просто интересно я смотри я живу в
California And me too  somehow it doesn't matter about
Калифорнии Да и мне как-то всё равно на
Zelensky Well, the Ukrainians are all well, he's
Зеленского Да ну украинцы все ну это
their president yes And what's the joke then,
ихний президент да А в чём тогда прикол
that you're a simple guy who's from
что вот ты простой парень который ты из
what city in general where do you live
кого города вообще там где-то где живёшь
spa Well, you can't have the Supreme Court
спа Ну тебе не может быть у него ВС
anyway if you're asking about him I'm from
равно если ты про него спрашиваешь Я из
Samara Samara yes, look, Samara is,
Самары Самары да вот смотри Самара это ж
in short, several thousand kilometers from
короче несколько тысяч километров от
Zelensky Yes, he touched you,
Зеленского Да он на тебя трогал он
he didn't know at all About your existence
вообще он не знал Про твоё существование
and the Ukrainians didn't know About your
и украинцы не знали Про твоё
existence Why do you feel bad about him
существование Почему ты вот плохо к нему
what happened to you personally in Samara that
что случилось у тебя лично в Самаре что
you started to feel bad about
ты плохо начал относиться к
Zelensky Well, like a special military
зеленскому Ну как специальна военная
operation has begun, not a special military
операция началась не специальная военная
operation has begun yes, why do you feel bad
операция началась да ты почему плохо Вот
Putin has started a special military operation,
Путин начал специальную военную операцию
he has started to feel bad about Zelensky
он плохо начал относиться к зеленскому
because he's fighting with him yes And you're a
потому что он с ним воюет да А ты
simple guy from Samara Why
простой парень из Самары Почему из-за
because Putin started a special military
того что Путин начал специальную военную
operation Yes, he kills people and you started to
операцию Да убивает людей а ты начал
feel bad about those he kills,
плохо относиться к тем кого убивает в
what's the
чём
joke and how should I feel good about him,
прикол а как я к нему должен хорошо
you can feel neutral, good Well,
относиться можно нейтрально хорошо Ну а
why bad and you say that
плохо за что и ты говоришь что потому
because a special military operation  operation Well,
что специально военная операция Ну то
that is, I say Putin took and made a war
есть говорю Путин взял сделал войну
of conquest and attacked, but I don’t know what’s the joke with those who were
захватнические напал а к тем на кого
attacked, I
напали в чём
can’t answer this
прикол не знаю не смогу ответить на этот
question why Let’s try Look, I’m
вопрос почему Давай пробуем смотри я же
not asking you to come up with some kind of
не прошу чтобы ты прямо вот какой-то
precise question like on an exam, just so that
точный как на экзамене вопрос просто
we have versions like this in your
чтобы мы версии вот вот как у тебя в
head It just sat down with you, someone planted it in you,
голове Оно ж у тебя село кто-то тебе это
it developed in you Yes, why is
заложил оно у тебя развилось Да почему
it lying in your head Why do you
оно лежит у тебя в голове Почему ты
hate Zelensky Yes, because he’s
ненавидишь Зеленского Да из-за того что
doing
идёт
his own Well, how does he sponsor his
сво Ну как он же спонсирует свою
army, right Well, that’s his surrender, he’s the
армию правильно Ну вот его э сдача он
president of a country that is defending itself from an
президент страны которая защищается от
aggressor, of course, he should sponsor an
агрессора конечно он должен спонсировать
army, this is how they
армию это
kill our people, right Why
убивают наших людей правильно Почему
Because your people attacked this,
Потому что ваши люди напали на это так
just like, for example, when the police
же как например полицейские когда
kill a bandit, he does well because
убивает бандита он хорошо делает потому
he is defending, and when a bandit kills a
что он защищает а бандит когда убивает
policeman, he does badly, so it turns out
полицейского он плохо так получается
Russia, like a bandit, attacked Ukraine, this is
Россия как бандит напала на Украину это
normal, any country, according to the UN statute,
же нормально любая страна по статуту ООН
must defend itself and kill aggressors
должна защищаться и убивать агрессоров
That is, what Zelensky and the
То есть то что делает Зеленский и
Armed Forces of Ukraine are doing  and We from America
Вооружённые силы Украины и Мы из Америки
help the armed forces of Ukraine Yes,
помогаем вооружённым силам Украины Да
here is the denazification
вот денацификация
cauldron a little Yes, old man And now
котел немножко Да старичок А сейчас
young Trump is active there now he
молоденький Трамп активный там сейчас он
will make him a big leather shell
его сделает ему большой кожанный снаряд
on Kola put no one no one has
на Коле постави никто никто не ставил
ever put a tram I mean no one has ever
никогда трам В смысле никто никогда
always in short Russia look Russia
всегда короче Россия смотри Россия
Russia has never won a single war
Россия не выигрывала ни одной войны
on its own Russia has only won
самостоятельно Россия выигрывала только
in coalition with America, Britain and
в коалиции с Америкой британией там и
other countries that's all they lost to the Japanese
другими странами вот и всё японцам
themselves Yes, they lost against Napoleon
проиграли сами Да вот против Наполеона
then too, like damn, they burned
проиграли тогда тоже типа блин сожгли
Moscow down in general the Tatars and the Mongols lost
Москву вообще татаро монголам проиграли
everything, [ __ ]
все прова
[music]
[музыка]
burn what war did Russia win Moscow
сжи какую войну Россия выиграла Москву
Moscow Why
Москву Зачем
did they burn it down why did they burn it down because they
сожгли зачем зачем сожгли потому что
got beat up at Borodino they ran away
получили звездюлей под Бородино убегали
and fled
и сбегали
Moscow Well, they did the right thing because there
Москву Ну ну правильно сделали потому
was no other choice Well, that is, you
что выбору другого не было Ну то есть вы
lost Borodino they burned it down oh, at Borodino
проиграли Бородино сожгли ой в Бородино
you got beat up and ran away burned
получили вы звездюлей убежали сожгли
your capital and fled somewhere into the woods
свою столицю и убежали где-то в леса
Napoleon and the result of the war  what was the outcome of the war
Наполеон а итог войны какой итог войны
you lost Napoleon returned uh to
вы проиграли Наполеон вернулся э в во
France because in France the
Францию потому что во Франции началось
revolutionary uprising began again Yes he
революционное Восстание снова Да он
returned there and then the coalition uh
вернулся туда а потом коалиция э
Britain Sweden Austria And so on
Британия Швеция Австрия И так дальше
Italy Anti-Napoleonic coalition Yes
Италия Анти наполеоновская коалиция Да
he was
его
defeated and when we lost to the Japanese
победила а японцам мы когда проиграли
905 Russo-Japanese War
905 русско-японская война
Yeah and forty-fifth
Угу а сорок пятый
and forty-fifth look forty-fifth you were
а сорок пятый смотри сорок пятый вы были
in the coalition not You first of all yes Vova not
в коалиции не Вы во-первых да Вовы не
Russia but it was the Soviet Union it
Россия а было это Советский Союз это
was with the Ukrainians with the Belarusians with the Kazakhs
были с украинцами с белорусами с
and so on in the coalition with the
казахами и так дальше в коалиции с
Americans with the French with the British
американцами с французами с британцами
it was a coalition of just the strongest
это была коалиция как раз сильнейших
powers Yes European and American and
держав Да европейских и американских а
you yourself did not win anything well really at
сами вы ничего не выиграли ну реально
least one war that you yourself won
хоть одну войну которую вы выиграли сами
in Afghanistan got involved in lost and
в Афганистан влезли проиграли
left and you did not lose in
ушли а вы не проиграли в
Afghanistan who were you anyway why did you
Афганистане ккто вы туда вообще зачем
go there Well America America did not enter
пошли Ну Америка Америка не входила в
Afghanistan but only shot from behind a huge wall
Афганистан а только из-за стены огромной
no America helped the local
стреляли нет Америка помогала местной
authorities then look you are running away from the
власти то ты смотри ты ты убегаешь от
main question Yes what war  Russia
главного вопроса Да какую войну Россия
won on its own without the help of
выиграла самостоятельно без помощи
America, Britain, France, Sweden, and so
Америки Британии Франции Швеции И так
on, at least one. Name it really.
дальше хоть одну Назови реально
Well, I don’t know specifically Russia, because
Ну конкретно Россия не знаю потому что
for 20 years, even the Russian Empire, the
за 20 лет Даже даже Российская империя
Soviet Union, we’ve been winning, no, where are you
Советский Союз побеждаем нет как Где вы
winning? Well, listen, it’s funny. You
побеждает Ну слушай смешно Мы в Америке
know, you’re already laughing in America. Since August 6, you can’t.
знаешь уже ржом вы с 6 августа не можете
It’s been six months, probably. You ca
это уже сколько полгода наверное прошло
n’t recapture part of your Kursk region.
не можете часть своей Курской области
That you’re winning. You’re
отвоевать что вы побеждает вы Э
reporting that you’ve taken some force for
рапортует что вы какое-то сило взяли на
three houses. In short, having put down
три хаты Да положив короче блин
several thousand of your own people there, that is,
несколько тысяч людей своих там то есть
it’s laughing at us. Uh, Peter Jackson, a
это смеётся у нас ээ Питер Джексон ээ на
military analyst, is speaking on CN. He’s
CN выступает военный аналитик он он
laughing. He’s taking. In short, he’s
смеётся он берёт короче аналитику
showing analytics. Russia captured the village of
показывает Россия захватила село
Novoselov. No matter where they
Новосёлов как куда не
ran. He hasn’t told us about Pete Jackson yet. The
убегали ещё про пита Джексона не
gray matter
серое вещество
is spinning. Everything is
закрутилось всё
spinning. Come on, turn on the gray matter.
походу го давай включай серое вещество
What kind of guy. He’s really in a stupor.
Какое и пацан Да он реально в ступоре Да
Why does he hate Zelensky?
за что он ненавидит Зеленского по вот
That’s not a great conversation. It’s a pity that the guy got
так не клас разговор Жалко что Парниша
stuck. It was possible to torture him longer and
завис можно было дольше его помучить и
show that he’s in  bashke anro the
показать что у не в башке анро самый
coolest psychotherapist gets everything out of them
классный психотерапевт вытягивает из них
like subscribe comment Slava Ukraine
всё лайк подписка комент Слава Украине
subscribe to my Instagram I don't know
подпишись на мий Instagram Я не знаю для
why it's for you why else you should watch
чого це тоб для чого ще тоб там дивитись
on my face But for you it's one
на оцей мий фейс Але для тебе це один
two or three clicks But you try me and I
два або три клика Але ты тримае мене и я
will Kata va in me there are a bunch of fouls and
буду Ката ва в мене там Купа фолов и
I will be in a cool mood to do
мене буде классный настрий щоб робити
New cool video letter to my Instagram
Нови крут видео пись на мий Instagram
Popik Andriy
Попик Андрий
then Come on I'm
отак Давай я тебя
waiting for you L
чекаю L